To be honest, if you play Delta recently as a taxi game,
Then you're playing it wrong. Now it is more suitable to play Delta as a BOSS game.
If you accidentally bump into one of the five engineering masters in the game, then congratulations,
What you are facing is no longer an operator, but a monster. I won't blame you for failure here,
Because of encountering this kind of monster, Ultraman had to hide the transformer and then grab the lost bag.
My leather friend doesn’t play anymore. Tan Xiaojian came to the second game, and no matter how many times he counted, he felt that he was one team behind on the field.
We found this rat, so good, people should be up now, right? Hey, holy shit, what kind of gun is this?
Brother, this pedicure spray is best used on your back! Of course,
I'm not stupid enough to turn a blind eye when I see hidden dangers. So, I tried to use the tacit understanding among savages to
Tell him to drop that pedicure spray. Stop pretending, you have it, you have it, you have it, you have it, you have it,
Hurry up!
Throw it away, let you withdraw. oops! After some negotiation, Shushu chose to give up the opportunity.
Well, we are not trying to kill everyone. Let’s go and evacuate together. So if nothing unexpected happens,
It's time for an accident. At the last minute, the sound of continuous sniping came. Hey,
Seeing the sniper kid bullying my teammates, I immediately felt protective. What?
After a roar, my brain shut down because I was so angry.
When I reacted, I fired a few shots.
The protectiveness has gone down again, goodbye to my teammates, see you in the south. Unexpectedly, one jet went too far.
It sprayed directly to the Antarctic. Well, since the Antarctic side is relatively cold,
So our three operators automatically turned into N-two. I'm not happy to play with this kind of operator.
Who chose this for me? Come on, after you become the CEO, you will see a couple on your face. I don’t know if the opponent will give up or not.
Anyway, I'm done with it. Ah, do you want to give up? Hahahahaha! Cooperate with teammates to succeed.
After knocking down one of them, I was about to hit the state, when I suddenly heard my teammates begin to shout eagerly: "Hit!
Hit! Hit! "Now, hit!" Hit! All hit! Really? Really? Really?
Really? Really hit! All hit! One on the left, awesome! The story develops here,
Except for me evolving to second life, everything else was actually pretty smooth. Well, as we all know,
The development of most stories always involves some unexpected plots.
لغات.
Those who are playing dirty tricks are kicked by those who are fiercely attacking, and those who are playing dirty tricks are kicked by those who are playing dirty tricks. It turns out that the issue of operator strength does not affect me.
Anyway, no matter what others do, I will always get kicked. Although I have become such a coward,
But I still firmly believe that fools are always blessed. Does anyone want it? And this, your equipment,
Your equipment, you rent it well, you can take it, you can take it, you really don’t need it, I rented it well.
But I couldn't come.